This is Selizamoa, proceeding today.
This is the 182nd edition of Ukka's Delightful and Fufu Showroom.
I would like to deliver this edition with a new subtitle.
Please do.
Decide the subtitle with the users here,
We will decide the subtitle with the users here, and deliver the program based on the subtitle.
So there is almost no script.
Please do so.
So, I will show you the original rules of Ukka,
I will show you the original rules of Ukka.
First of all, we are going to do a delivery named after it, which is Ukka's original rule. There is almost no script, so please understand.
So, that's the proposed subtitle,
We don't have anything seasonal for today,
For example, it could be something like, "Golden Week, Good job!
Please send me whatever you think would be good.
Please send whatever you think would be good.
What would you like?
Are you waiting?
I'm stuck.
Another special for the tummy.
Here you go. Good job.
Thank you very much.
Thanks for your help.
Are you excited to dress up my pattern?
What do you like?
What do you like? What do you like? What do you like?
Tired type?
I'm going to go with the tired type.
What kind of music?
Exciting?
Is it the Skeetbus one?
Moyamoya?
What do you got?
Sign for look back four beats, five down.
Can-Go.
How about a link to just Can-Go?
I think it's good.
How about a link just for Can-Go?
I think it's good I think it's good I think it's good I think it's good I think it's good I think it's good I think it's good I like it
How about it? I think it's good.
It's settled.
It's decided.
Okay, the subtitle should be "Can We Go Back to Golden Week?
Yes. So now that we have decided on today's subtitle, I would like to make the title call. Uguka's, Delightful, Anxious, Boy-Moo, Can-Go-Back Golden Week!
Yes, that's right, good evening everyone. We are Uka.
Yes, I, Sherry-chan, will also bring you today's proceedings.
It's Golden Week, the end of Golden Week,
I will ask you to do your best. I look forward to working with you.
Then, Yume-chan, please introduce yourself. Me first?
Yes, I am Mei Kawasaki. Please do.
Yes, I'm Akane Sora. Nice to meet you.
Yes, this way.
Thank you for visiting the 182nd Ukka's Delightful and Hip-Hop Showroom today.
Thank you very much.
Oh, it's like I'm going back.
Um, we have this here.
You know, the channel.
You know?
So, you know, I understand it.
I want to go back to summer, you know, what our song means.
I want to go back.
I want to go back. So, I want to go back to Golden Week.
I'd love to.
I want to go back.
I would like to do a quick spread time here.
In order to get as many people as possible to see this distribution, I'm going to tweet an announcement on Twitter now, so please tweet to everyone.
Please do.
So what shall I do? I'll remember.
I'm going to express with my body what I enjoyed the most during Golden Week.
The things I enjoyed.
That's the best, isn't it?
For fans,
For example, if you came to Lily Bay,
For example, Lily Bay in Tokodame,
or "Daida-chan was so cute at Shinjuku Marine View," whatever,
It would be great if you could write about what impressed you during Golden Week.
I am glad to hear you write about what impressed you during the Golden Week.
Thank you very much.
What did you think?Did you think about it?
Yes, I did.
What do you think?
Well, yes. I understand.
OK.
Okay, let's go.
What was impressive.
Okay.
Are you coming?
Thank you for joining us for the first time BDM. You're here.
Shall we go then?
Yes, let's go.
All right, let's go!
543215, four, three, two, one.
Okay, thank you very much.
Are we done?
Sake.
Good night.
Still good... the shadows were strong.
The harder you tried, the prettier you were.
Nervous about being too close to Shinjuku than home for the first time.
Indeed.
There's no har tension, either.
Recently
In Nishinamiya's after-hours graffiti
I miss that the sound stopped for a moment
Indeed.
Ah, it stopped.
It flowed, properly.
A lot has happened, but thank you all for coming.
Yes, I know I just talked a bit, but I would like to talk about our Golden Week.
First of all, we have decided to release our first major single on Wednesday, June 21. We are.
Yes, we are.
We have 317 release events, and we had the release on April 29 at Shinjuku Lime Rooftop.
Yes, we are. Thank you very much.
How many years has it been since you were at this venue?
It's been two years, or maybe a year and ten times? How many years has it been since I was at this venue?
How many years has it been?
It's been about 10 years.
It's been three years, three years since I've been here, but the design of the stage hasn't changed at all, so I remember it fondly.
It was a lot of fun.
And the next day, Sunday, April 30,
We held a mini-live for the release of our first major single!
Thank you very much.
This was a live performance that I personally loved.
I'm sure.
I don't know if you saw it,
I don't know if you saw it or not, but... I don't know if you all saw it, but if you were able to see it, you were lucky if you were able to make it.
I don't know what I'm talking about, but please watch the show if it comes up again.
It's been a long time since I've done this... about a year.
It's been a long time since I've delivered a live broadcast via e-mail, which is rare, I hear.
And on Sunday, May 2nd, I'm going to be on the youtube live show Talkie Avert Session 2.
I've been doing this for a long time. I was in a session with Schencher and who? Huh? But, you know, I came out. No, I was typing.
I was typing on my phone,
It didn't come up?
It's a season.
We had a Season 2.
Thank you very much.
This is us,
This is the third time we have appeared in the show.
This is the third time we have performed here,
This time we performed with AmeFlash and two other groups.
We performed with Mr. AmeFlash this time, but I can't say I felt the same tension as before.
I was very nervous about the tension between the two groups, but it was rare to have two groups perform.
It was a rare opportunity to have two groups perform together, and it was a lot of fun.
I was so happy to be able to nominate Mr. Simas for the first time, but it wasn't me, it was the one who was nominated for the second time,
I was nominated the second time, so I will leave it here. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Oh, if you get along with Mr. Alfera, yes.
Um, a little bit, uh, if you get along with Mr. Anuhera, yes.
I talked a little bit. I'm good friends with Yu,
We went home together. With Yu.
We talked and went home together.
Also, Rina and I get along well with Hana-chan,
It's not that we don't get along that well,
But we don't have a chance to talk much,
So, I do not have much opportunity to talk with them.
Think of it as a play.
Yes, it was like that.
On May 4, we had a concert at the Lily Bay Aeon Mall in Tomozaru.
Thank you very much.Thank you very much.
It's the first time in a year, isn't it?
It's been a year since I've been here, and this venue was great, and it was sunny at the beginning of those four days, and I thought it would be a good start for me.
Then, if the weather was good, it would have been on the second day.
We performed at Aichi Sky Expo Central Stage.
Thank you very much for your kind attention.
I thought it was a very cool and nice situation.
Last time we were inside, so it was fun to see people outside for the first time.
Please come again!
The next day, May 6, I spoke at the Minis event at Nishinomiya Gardens. This is Hyogo Prefecture, so,
It was the first time for us to go to Hyogo prefecture,
How was it?
What was it like?
It was raining.
That's right.
But I have a lot of friends who like Takarazuka,
When I got off at the station, I saw "Takarazuka" written on the station,
When I got off at the station, I saw Takarazuka written on the station sign, and I felt that Hyogo was a great place to visit,
The stage was open in a way I had never seen before, and it was a lot of fun. The stage was open in a way that I had never seen before, and it was a lot of fun.
I hope you will invite us again.
I'd love to have you back again.
The last day was the release event on May 7 at Yotobashi Camera Multimedia Umeda.
Thank you very much.
It was raining so hard!
But we were happy to be indoors that day.
I think the rain didn't do too much damage to the audience.
We also had the opportunity to speak out, so...
It was the last day of the event, and there was a lot of enthusiasm.
I think it was a good last day of Golden Week.
Thank you very much.
It was hot, wasn't it?
Yes, it was.
It was great for 4 days.
Thank you to those who came to all of them and to those who came to some of them.
Thank you very much.
It was fun to feel the thrill, wasn't it?
Yes, it was. And I think that the night and the idol channel, which is my personal channel, has been up from Saturday, May 6 to today, May 10.
I think it will be up on Wednesday in the evening, and I'd like to invite anyone who wants to know more about me and my work, or even if you know me, to come and watch.
I hope you will watch it.
I'm really grateful to you.
Thank you very much.
I had a lot of fun. - Thank you very much.
I'd like to go the other way.
It's Golden Week, that's why we're here.
The project is Hearing Golden Week
Please tell us in the comments how you spent your Golden Week!
I mean other than Uka related
What kind of Golden Week did you spend outside of Uka?
Did you spend it? Golden Week other than Uka.
What did you do? What did you do?
I'm sure many of you can't comment, right?
I mean, other than Uka-related things.
Maybe not even for a long time.
I know, right? I mean, other than Uka-related things.
If you go on an expedition, it will be outside of the live concert.
That's right. You mean, what did you do?
I wonder if it's daytime activities.
Going back to my parents' house and feeling nature. That's nice. It's really nice.
So your parents' house is a nature place?
That's right. It's funny looking at Yamato and all.
Wait. What?
I haven't seen your wife in a while... but maybe it's because I've been gone for 4 days and I don't have to go tomorrow.
I've been away from work, avoiding work, avoiding work, avoiding work.
Repeat.
Oh, I got it with the outdoor lox.
Nice.
Overseas.
Yes, it is.
Sesame.
I drank with him for the first time when he came to visit me.
I'm sure the old man is right...
I'm sure you're going to feel something when you go to the curb, I wonder what it's going to be called?
I think it's not... I was at Smarhammer Drive, a beach driveway in Ishikawa Prefecture.
Ishikawa, huh? I can't really imagine it.
Smarhama Drive? On the beach?
Sounds interesting. Wow, that's great.
Sounds interesting. That's great. I want to go to Ishikawa Prefecture.
Don't put it in the tire. It looks like it's going to fit.
In the tire.In tires.
Cleaned up.
We had a pizza party.
Some picnic.
Picnic. Was it nice weather?
This way. How was it?
No, but I think it was raining.
I wonder if it was raining.
With a guy named Pizza Pawpaw. Pizza Powie? No, but I think he was typing that. He's got a lot of hand dacoits.
He's been playing with his hands. Supporting half of the body with one-way support.
I've been working with a guy I went to high school with.
High school classmates.
They're all on break, so we'll get to meet them.
It's nice. I miss it.
I picked out a pillowcase... and I love it. I used to do the laundry on a daily basis.
Did you miss it when you came home? I did.
I missed sleeping in my own bed. I almost cried.
I thought I was gonna cry.
I asked my mom to do the laundry, even though I wasn't there.
I asked her to wash my pillowcases, too, since I didn't wear mids and stuff.
The everyday stuff, like taking out the trash. I came home and it was so dirty.
My sister had trashed the place and left clothes and leftovers that weren't mine.
It's not good.
Someone can't live there.
It was really today, though.
What else?
So far I've been to Osaka.
Thank you very much.
This is Eggs Sigs with Eggs.
Benevicto.
I had some.
What kind of eggs?
The kind with the egg on the bread.
It's got a half-boiled egg on it.
It's delicious.
It looks so delicious.
It's good on the inside, too.
What else?
Summer goods processing.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
I've been working with the cats! I'm sorry I had to leave work to get the cat grounded.
Cat. Oh, I see.
Cats, right.
I've been watching cartoons.
It's really popular right now.
It's amazing.
A shinoko.
A man-cat.
A man's son.
Take a look.
I'm curious.
But there were also a lot of people who seemed to have been at the Uguka concert,
They seem to be doing a lot of different things.
I guess they seem to like it a lot. I'm glad. You seem to be doing a lot of different things.
I'm glad.
Golden Week is great, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
How many days was that?
Nine days?
Nine years.
Nine years?
That's nice.
I'd like to go on a trip or something.
Yeah.
After all, I realized that the local sashimi konnyaku is the best.
Eh? Local sashimi konnyaku? Because I realized that it is the most delicious. What? Local sashimi konnyaku?
It's good to be aware of it.
I learned a lot.
You learned a lot. I'm learning from now on.
About your participation in the Koeda City Alifes after a long absence.
That's right. There seem to be quite a lot of Koeda City Accounting Arifeng sites around here, so hmmm...
I heard that you were attending the class.
I'm a parent, so I'm going with this?
But we don't know that my sister was doing this.
It's just the way it is in some places.
I see.
She never takes a day off.
We only eat once.
That's ideal.
I like that. That's pretty much it. It's ideal, though.I like that. It's ideal, though.
Many of you go to festivals, don't you?
Yes, they do.
There are a lot of festivals in June?
June festivals.
Yes, they do.
So there are a lot of festivals. Yeah.
I prayed about Ukka at Hanazono Shrine.
Thank you very much.
Thank you so much.
So this is how it's going to be.
Thank you very much.
I hope everyone is having fun.
They look like they're having fun.
Inside the Ukkan.
Inside the Ukkan. We'd love to have you. Sounds like fun. I'm looking forward to it.
We'd love to have you.
I don't get it.
I'm sure there are a lot of people out there.
I was watching the streaming of the festival while I was at work.
I was watching it while I was at work.
I wonder how they are watching it.
Is it like voiceless?
Or do you have your earphones in?
I don't know, if that's what you do, you can do it.
Lucca and three nights, no.
Thank you very much.
Stay overnight. Stay overnight. Wait for me. Wait for it. Lucca got me hooked on Lucca, which I did a lot of today. I'm glad.
I'm glad.
Thank you very much.
I hope you two will come to the site someday.
I would love to have your release.
This photo conquest.
Real.
I know, right?
CDs and such are piling up.
There will be many more to come. Everyone.
That's right.
You know what?
The more you attend the benefit parties and stuff, the better.
I joined the FC.
Thank you very much.
Inadvertently?
I joined by accident.
Telework.
If it's telework, sure.
You know, there are people from Alien Corner who are doing this telework, right?
He came to the talk port.
And when I said hello, he was on a balance ball like this.
I can do that because I telework, can't I?
Yes, I can probably do it because I telework.
I always do it with a balance ball because I telework.
It's a little hard to make it like that, though.
It was interesting.
Is this your first time at Uguka, Satsuka?
This happened by chance.
It was a sudden decision, that's for sure.
Satsuka Yuubu's. I'm grateful. I'm glad. It was decided suddenly. Thank you.
I'm glad you took it.
I had an acquaintance.
Even though I was on site, Momochan went.
Thank you. Last time?
What happened? I got to meet some of your fans.
We see a lot of the same faces when we're together for a few days.
And you get to know them well. No matter who you put a sheet on.
Maybe one day we'll have a circle in one lump.
Maybe it would be great to see it.
Please show us.
I want you to talk more with Yamae-chan than with your parents during Golden Week.
You should talk more.
Why aren't you talking?
I'll tell you why.
No way.
I'm so happy.
Everyone was wearing a lot of clothes.
Yes, live.
Everyone's out and about.
Osuka.
We have meetings.
We are also coming to Machida.We are also coming to Machida.
Oh, so you will come to Machida on the 14th, please.
Thank you very much for telling us about your home situation.
It's something I've never done before.
Next time, let's go to the next one. Next project, here we go.
Brush up on Golden Week!
This Golden Week, Uka was thankfully super busy.
However, back to Golden Week once again,
Let's look back and post from the perspective of the world that enjoyed the rapid consecutive holidays!
I see.
That's good. That thing you say.
I want to take a holiday with a payroll.
You mean, what did I do?
Ideal.
There's a staff down here.
Yes. 3. 3.
Three. three.
Q is big.
Please let me know if you want to go into makeup with this.
I don't think so.
What should we do?
I'll think about it. I know.
Because everyone else isn't here.
I have a lot of time. I can do whatever I want.
That's right.
I'm not sure what everyone else is going to do, all of a sudden.
So is everyone else.
Yeah, yeah.
Tell me about it.
I'll think about it in real life.
Okay, I'm going to go in now, and it's time for Golden Week.
Let's take a look back.
Well, I was on vacation.
I know you've already taken care of me.
This is the first time I've done 9 episodes.
Really.
I went to see the closing. I'm sorry.
That's okay.
I thought this was the only way to heal.
During this period.
I was trying to see how I could be spared,
You have given me lots and lots of love.
That's nice.
It was like that.
It's like the only thing I can think of is guesses.
It's full of guessing events.
That's right. I'm trying to do something like this,
Like pictures and stuff.
I took pictures. That's nice.
You did it, didn't you?
What did you do? Holding eek.
I sailed around the world.
You know, they often put them up in the bathrooms.
You know, the ones that say you can go around the world.
I thought I'd give it a try,
So I did it. I went there during this period of time.
What impressed you the most?
Well, I don't know. I had never been to India, and I had never been to India.
I had never been to India, and all I could think of was curry.
But it was not only curry, but also a lot of spices.
Yes, there were a lot of spices. There must have been a lot of spices.
It was a very enjoyable India.
It was a very enjoyable time in India. The boat trip left a strong impression of India, didn't it? There was a lot of fun in India, too! AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!! AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!! AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!! AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!! AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!! Ohhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh, I slept for like 7 days while on break? Huh? Parents and stuff?
They didn't say anything.
Parents?
I didn't sleep.
I thought maybe they had something to eat or drink while they were asleep.
While I was sleeping.
I'm here for sustenance.
I don't remember,
I didn't wake up feeling hungry or anything,
Maybe it was a forced illness.
I'm sure it's there.
When I found out, I probably went and got it and drank it,
I woke up for a day and did the assignment anyway,
And then I was done.
I see.
Did you have any dreams?
I might have dreamed.
Did you have any impressive dreams?
Did you have any impressive dreams? What about impressive dreams?Did you have any impressive dreams? What was your most memorable dream?
I was at a concert.
Uka was performing,
And..,
Moa-chan was falling down.
What? Isn't that a dream?
Were you okay?
I was fine.
That happened, didn't it? It was a fun show, despite the incident.
I see.
Thank you very much.
It seems like everyone came to the show.
Do you want to ask them?
Yes, I will. What are you guys doing?
Well, you know, I found this place.
Yeah, yeah.
You can do whatever you want with it.
What were we doing?
We all need to take a break.
Everybody take a break.
Oh, my God,
You should have said that earlier.
I'm sorry.
That's great.
We've all been overdoing it.
Oh, yeah.
I've been living it. And then.
She said she was a grandmother. That's nice.
That's a normal, nice story. This.
They got married. Congratulations.
Okay, but I don't want you to cut back on the 4-day field trip.
Even if you get married.
I'd appreciate it if you don't reduce the number of sites.
I don't know if it's a good idea to start with the search for a new bride, but if you have something like this, I'd be happy to help.
I'm not sure if the nine of us can start out looking for a
I'm sure you'll have a blast with Emma.
I've been getting blasted every day with rice, and I'm getting blasted in Europe, and I'm sorry to say that I'm a little out of shape in Europe, but I think it's easier to get my balls in the air every day.
I'm sorry, but I think it's easier to go to Europe if you do it every day.
It's a fermentation process.
It takes a lot of time.
Load up roses...
I'm going to go to the gym and get super macho.
I wonder how long it takes.
If you have this place, you can get used to it.
I can get macho.
I was lost in Binos Iris.
How's he doing? Did he make it? This one.
I think he's gonna make it. I think so.
Where?
Where? It's out of the country, isn't it?
What? Where is it?
Maybe Japan.
What? No, it's not Japan. Not Japan. It's not Japan.
Where is it?
Paris? Like Paris!
You know it?
I think.
The elephant.
Asian?
You mean they have moai elephants?
That's close enough.
I wonder where the moai elephants are.
It's not like in India or something.
Oh, I know exactly where it is!
You know what I mean? Yui, you know what I mean? I don't know.
Maybe you do, but I don't understand it at all.
France?
Totally the opposite.
The opposite? The other way around?
Russia?
Uh, no.
I don't know the names of the districts.
America?
Argentina.
Argentina!
Uh...
What's near Argentina?
Brazil.
Oh, yeah, that one, that one, what's near Argentina? Brazil.
That way.There you are.
Argentina?
I was so confused.
I'd like to get lost in Argentina.
Argentina.
Argentina!
I was like, "Argentina, come to me, Peace.
Like, you can do Argentina.
I see.
So you're a whole person.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
It was a nice Golden Week, wasn't it?
Thank you very much.
I would like to play the next song now.
Go Back Golden WeekI would like to read the next song. For the Go Back Golden Week song, let's go back to Golden Week just for a moment and reenact for a moment the most memorable scenes from this year's Golden Week.
I see.
But when I say the most, I'm thinking of the overture at Nishinomiya,
But Ruri, you're not far away.
The stage at that time,
There was no front room,
There was no front room, so we went directly from the dressing room to the stage.
The distance from the backstage to the stage was huge,
We had to go to the stage in the middle of the overture to make it in time.
So I asked Rui, "Shouldn't you go to the stage already?
Shouldn't we go? I said to Rui, "You should go. I said to Rui, "You should go,
I told Rui that she should go, and she started walking really fast.
And I got to the stage before my turn to perform.
There was an awkward moment when I was alone,
It was a bit awkward,
But Rui's not here these days.
It was really funny. That was the most interesting moment, but Rui is not here. That was so much fun, wasn't it?
That was the funniest.
By yourself?
It was fun.
It was interesting.
But it was too intense,
Lori looked really embarrassed.
Me too.
I really like it.
It was really interesting, wasn't it? It really was.
I don't know.
Was it funny?
A little bit.
Impression.
No impression?
Impression?
Well, what?
I don't even remember what it's like anymore.
Oh, I see.
I remember playing dice.
Dice... dice... not so much. I remember playing dice.
Dice, right, we rolled dice, right?
We rolled dice, right?
We did.
We ate pasta.
We ate pasta. We drank mango juice.
I was just wondering about your comment,
In the Shinjuku 2-part overture.
I heard that Ayame and Ruri were slid in the second overture in Shinjuku.
What does that mean?
Overture is a slide?
Does it mean they are in different positions?
Oh, is that what it means?
Maybe it's like, what was the number, 4?
Was it 4? 4, 4,
Okay, so maybe you were in 2.5 and Louis was in 2.5.
What number?
He said, "This way.
Oh, that's it!
Then he said, "This way.
So that's how it is.
So he did it.
I'm sure it's true, that overture, you know...
When the number is 3 or 4 or 5, when the member in front of you happens to be different, you don't know what to do.
You don't know whether you should say it or not.
But, you know, maybe when you stand up, you feel differently. It's difficult, isn't it? It's difficult, isn't it?But, you know, maybe if I stood up, it would feel different. Like that. It is difficult, isn't it?
What was the most impressive thing for you?
I don't know. I don't know. What was impressive? I can't say.
I can't say.
I have no memory at all.
Wasn't it the benefit in Nishinomiya? Video.
Go for it, video.
That's right. That might have been a pretty interesting time for a benefit.
I'm filming a video at the Nishinomiya award show. video at the Nishinomiya benefit event,
I have about four candidates,
I have about four candidates for the "Ganbare! or "Go for it, musical style! or "Ganbare!
I shoot them,
There are about three of us. There are three members in the group,
And since everyone is in front of us, we take a video,
I had to put my shame aside. How can you take a video without being humiliated?
I was so nervous that it may have left a lasting impression on me.
I was so nervous about how to take a video without shame that it may have left a lasting impression on me,
I was taking videos at the same time, and the voices of the other members were included in the video that the fans uploaded,
But this time, it was one person at a time, and everyone stopped to look at me,
But this time, it was just one person at a time, and everyone stopped and looked at me, so I felt like, what am I going to do?
It was embarrassing.
Ayuru-chan's "Kozufuro Ganbarou" was the best.
What is that?
We played with Cosmic Flo at the Islamia concert, didn't we?
At that time, Mr. Mogu, who was behind me, was jumping by himself,
And, I don't know, only the audience was allowed to dance. The venue.
But everyone was doing it, right? That's just like....
Always.
But that day, only MOG was dancing,
And MOG was flying,
I thought it was over after the first turn, so I sat down once,
But the second turn came, so I had to get up again.
That's right. It's a good atmosphere when it's over after the first turn, isn't it?
You know, "Hey, do it.
That's it,
That was really fun,
During the "Go for it" video, I was saying "Go for it" with the Cosmic Float.
I felt sorry for him because he was flying alone.
I was flying by myself, and I was just feeling sorry for myself.
All around, you know, flying at all.
I was on my own.
Maybe that's the best thing.
Maybe that's the best.
Yeah, sure. I was flying by myself. I was in the flower aisle at the time of the Shinjuku Wallemens,
When I did the Cosmic Blow, the fans were so close to me, I didn't know what to do.
I was so embarrassed.
I didn't feel like dancing,
I had to do something like this.
This is so bad.
What should I do?
I wondered how many turns I should make.
It had been a long time since I had been on the aisle, and I was so nervous.
I didn't know where to look.
It was surprisingly embarrassing to see the crowd.
Yes, it was very embarrassing.
But it was a reenactment. If I had to reenact, what would I do?
I'm going to reenact it at this time. What would you do if you had to reenact it? Oh, that's right. You said you're going to reenact this time now.
That's right.
I wonder. What was memorable for the members?
Was it something that happened because it was a live performance?
Oh, let's see... well... when you were licking your lips...
Um, when SHINee entered the stage, Sora made a huge mistake standing up and hitting the stage.
What?
I was really nervous when SHINee came in.
One more time, you know what?
The last song of JCIF,
I was in a hurry,
I was in a hurry, I didn't know where to go, where to go,
I was in a hurry, I didn't know where to go, where to go, where to go.
And I didn't know Sora-chan was doing this.
Kari-
No good.
Maybe that's it.
Maybe I made a mistake.
It's so easy to get caught,
Maybe that's it. Re-enactment. It's reproducing.
That's the point.
I didn't notice. I've been there before.
Shiny was terrible.
I have to keep saying shenanigans.Shenny must go on.
Yeah? I don't know where it is.
Was it a party before that?
No, it wasn't.
Uh..,
It was something,
It was over with the fucking shit-shit-shit-shit,
And then we'll just go "ta-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la.
I've got to go to the end,
I've got to go to the end now,
I've been in my position.
Which, which, which, which, which.
A blank head.
Really?
It's all white.
And the magnification hasn't changed.
The formation hasn't changed there.
It's all blank these days.
It was a bit fragile. That was a bit fragile.
They made a mistake yesterday, too.
Folkman. I always thought he was the one in front of me, doing up the sound of the handmade sandwiches and stuff.
Soba-chan in canon.
And the camera didn't bump into him.
It was the worst. Even for me.
It was so funny.
On the day of the show, we were told the timing,
We'd never done it before. I'd never done it before.
It was my first time,
I was told the timing, so I remembered it,
We did it about three times during rehearsal,
It was totally doable. At rehearsal.
It was just right on the spot.
But when it came time for the performance, I didn't know what to do. I chose her, but then I thought, "Everyone does it like this.
I thought I had bought this camera, but then I thought, "I'll take this one.
I thought you bought this camera. Like that. That's what makes me laugh.
I thought, "You don't see the chance, do you? I thought, "What am I going to do?
I thought, "What should I do?
That was really funny. That was...
No, it wasn't. I thought I was pretty calm,
But after we were done, Mariyu came over to me,
He said, "Sora-san, you made a mistake,
I thought he knew,
Of course he knew. I was just watching and doing my job.
Did you get it? I said, "Of course I didn't put my hand down,
Of course I didn't put my hand down,
What was the funniest thing was that his eyes were swimming.
I was so desperate to say, "I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
It really sucked.
But,
I'm going to try to get revenge on my own.
Isn't that unusual? It's quite rare,
To make a mistake.
Yes, it is.
Solo made a mistake,
I was so desperate.
Please sing with us again at 7 Colors Sotaba.
Yes, I would. It's also a good thing to make mistakes in live performances and such.
Ishino-san made a mistake in the lyrics.
And Ruri, too.
But I didn't make any mistakes.
I didn't make mistakes at all,
Slow motion, something,
She's in slow motion,
I'm thinking, "What does she mean by slow motion?
It's like, "I got it right, but I made a mistake, or I'm not making a mistake.
I'm in a hurry, I'm in a hurry, I'm in a hurry.
I'm in a hurry, I'm in a hurry.
Ruri is in Umeda, too,
It's difficult.
Have you ever skipped it?
You've made mistakes.
Kid,
Let's find the little mask. Like that.
Yes, yes, yes.
That was the first one.
The more I think about the lyrics...
I was like, "Oh, is this the lyric?
They were actually there, but all of a sudden I was making a fuss about it.
That's why I was making such a fuss all of a sudden, wasn't it?
But that's what happens when you're out in the real world.
That's what happens when you're out in the real world.It's what it's supposed to be.
Yeah, well...
But, you know, it's not good.
I'm sorry, but I've got a good reason.
I'm sorry, but there's a good reason.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
The ending of the 181st episode of Uguka's Delightful and Furufurufurufurana Showroom is here.
Here's the first one!
On Sunday, May 21st at Sanrio Puroland, we're going to have another show of our cute employees!
This is the first time for the six of us to perform here, although we did it once last year, so please come!
Tickets go on sale on April 29th, so please come. There will be a scoring session as well.
Please come!
Rina and Ruri are not here today, but here's some information about them... Saturday, June 3, at Studio Freedom, Studio Freedom, Shibuya, part of Yuukirina's birthday celebration.
Yuukirina's Birthday Solo Live, What's is?
What's is?
The second part was Ruri's birthday party.
Happy blue Ruri, cute but jam-packed!
This is the first time for these two to hold a solo birthday live, so please go and see them!
Please go!
Okay, next!
Uguka's one-man live shows will be held on Saturday, September 30 at Shibuya Beats, Saturday, October 14 at Tokyo Kinema Club, and on January 21 next year at Ebisu Liquid Room,
We will be performing at Liquid Room in Ebisu on January 21 next year.
The schedule has already been announced, so if you are free on these three days, please come and join us. If you are free, please come and see us on these three days.
And now, about the Lily Club.
This Sunday, May 14, we will be at Machida Terminal Plaza.
And on Saturday, May 20, we will be at La Laberdine and Hasukabe.
And Sunday, May 28 at Morishita Tsudanuma.
Sunday, June 4, Kodomari Little Festival and Underground Walkway.
Saturday, June 10: Kodomari Little Festival and Underground Walkway; Saturday, June 10: Raraport Tachikawa Tatsuki.
Sunday, June 11 is Komeidokuroku.
Yes, I have been to some of the venues.
Some of the venues I have been to before, and many of them are new to me,
Please come and visit us.
Thank you very much.
That's all for now.
Now, I would like to check the final ranking of the top 5.
Fifth place, Firefly Kikuchi. Thank you very much.
Fourth place, Mr. Q Icol MC Triangle T.
Thank you very much.
In third place, Daiki Iwaryu Shimao.
Second place, Rie Shibata.
Thank you very much.
First place, Mr. Isaku.
So, as you can see, the next broadcast will be on Wednesday, May 24th at 7:00 p.m. To make sure you don't miss any of the broadcasts, please mark your favorites with a heart mark.
Please check out the individual broadcasts as well, as they will all be broadcasted by Uguka's members.
If you have any comments on what I am saying in the broadcasts, please let me know.
Yes, that's why I'm not.
Yes, so that's all I have to say, Uka.
Thank you very much. I am in my house now. I'm in my house now. I'm in my house now.
I'm in my house now.
I'm in my house now. I'm in my house now. Thank you for your time. I haven't been able to do a lot of reflection lately because of the studio, but I heard that I can do it today, so thank you.
I don't have anything to say.
What is it?
Just chatting.
Chatting.
If you have anything you'd like to reflect on...
You can be a member or a commenter.
or in the comments
Please let us know.
I don't usually get a lot of reflection in the comments, so please let me know what you think.
You did it. I used to have a lot of them.
No, I've been stable lately.
You're too cute. I want you to be sorry.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for the broadcast. It really helped me get over my May blues.
It was good.
Thank you.
The way you cover up your mistakes is genius.
Is that it? Is it a live performance?Is that it? Is it a live show?
Is it a live show?
Thank you very much.
I was told by my Eggplant teacher that if I made a mistake, I should be able to cover it up.
If I don't say I made a mistake or something, I get told off for it.
Well, it's the same with MC.
That's right.
It was fun again!
Thank you very much.
You said four days in Kansai, but Aichi is in Tokai prefecture.
That's right.
Who started this?
The manager told me.
Aichi is not Kanto.
Kansai.
It's not Kansai.
He said, "Aichi is Kansai.
That's right.
From our point of view, it's west.
That's true.
What did you do for the Coordinating Committee, Mr. President?
I was working too. What did you do, Mr. President?
I was also working. Various.
I see.
Making ramen? I made ramen noodles.
I went to the swimming pool for my child for two days in a row.
I want to go to the pool.
Please take me there.
I'm not in the dressing room.
Isn't it too early for a pool? To the indoor pool.
That's great!
I wish we could go indoors more often.
You don't get chilled for hours.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm here to tell you that Team Orca is pissed at me.
Tokai Compliance.
It's a little, I don't know, I feel like Chili is still, you know, not good at Hashi.
Too weak.
That's right.
They've been on so many expeditions, but they have no idea what prefecture is in what region.
That's true. Maybe we should do a project like that.
A study project.
Have you crossed the border yet?
I'm curious.
I'm looking at Kelo.
How much do you care?
Teacher.
I swam as far as I could without getting my hair wet.
You're already transparent.
Why?
Why don't you get it wet from here?
Judrai asismento kusai.
It's too much trouble, it's too much trouble.
Let's start with Buenos Aires.
Argentina.
That's what it looks like.
I'll be on the bullet train soon.
We're only moving around.
We're taking the bullet train because we'll have nothing else to do but move around.
It's about time.
If you can say Shikoku's four prefectures, you'll be fine.
I can say it, I can say it, I can say it
I can say it.
Say them one at a time.
Let's finish with the last one.
Let's end with the last one.
Oh, it's so easy!
Kagawa.
Tokushima.
Ehime.
Just remember it with a song.
Remember with a song.
Seino.
Kochi.
Oh, I did it.
That's right.
Kochi, right?
Kochi, Kochi.
What's in Kochi? I said Kagawa. Kagawa, right? Coach, coach. What's with that?
Did you say Kagawa?
Kagawa, right?Kagawa left, right?
Yes, I did.
Yes, it was there.
It's the coach.
Coach!
That's right.
What were you doing?
It was there.
It's from the Momo Kuro song.
Yes, it is.
Very much so. I want it.
Then, please close it up.
Yes, I will. So, thank you all very much for watching the 182nd.
Thank you very much.
I have a lot of things planned for Uka as I mentioned earlier, so I would be very happy if you all could come by somewhere.
So that's all for now.
Bye bye.
bye-bye.